DEDE NURHADI PUTRA

Full Stack Developer

**** 082167500197 **Pandung, West Java** @ denurhadiputra@amail.com

https://denurhadiputra.my.id/

SUMMARY

An enthusiastic person who has strong interest in Web Developer and Software Developer. I am skilled in PHP, JavaScript, Rest API and have experience working for Web developer positions for 1+ years. I am looking for good opportunities in the future regarding my background and interest in Web Developer and Software Developer.

EXPERIENCE

Web Developer

Value Stream Internasional

iii 03/2023 - Present ♀ Bandung, West Java

PT. Value Stream Indonesia (VSI) is an IT company, formed to focus on managing the associated business transaction, one of which is a switching company and software developer to support online transaction.

- Bug fixes on web applications
- Develop the project with dev team using git
- Improve speed data processing and query for datatable
- Integration of libraries like laravel excel and pdf export into the project
- Integration of one project to another using APIs
- Worked with over 3+ small scale web based projects and 1+ large scale web applications

Back-End Developer

PT. Pesat Aghni Solusi

= 03/2022 - 09/2022

Bandung, West Java

PT. Pesat Aghni Solusi is an IT company based in an information systems laboratory.

- Bug fixes on web applications
- Make web service API with lumen
- Develop the project with the dev team using git and laravel modules
- Integration of libraries like laravel excel and pdf export into the project
- Worked with over 7+ small scale web based projects and 2+ large scale web applications

Freelance Web Developer

CV. Klik

iii 02/2022 - 02/2022 ♀ Bandung, West Java

CV. Klik is an IT consulting company engaged in website creation.

- Build a company profile site using Laravel, Bootstrap, and JQuery
- Hosting the website using cPanel
- Worked with over 15+ small scale web based projects and 2+ large scale web applications

EDUCATION

Informatics Engineering (unfinished)

Indonesian Computer University

High School

SMA Negeri 1 Kota Ternate

TRAINING / CERTIFICATION

Laravel Web Development

Responsive Web Design

Sanbercode | 2021

freeCodeCamp| 2021

Powered by Enhancy

TECH STACK

HTML	CSS	SCSS Bootstrap		TailwindCSS	JavaScript		JQuery	ReactJS	VueJS	NextJS	APIs
Postman	PHP	My:	SQL Laravel	Phalcon	Git	Github	Gitlab	Microso	ft Office		